{"data":[{"question":"That was one of the most beautiful campuses we _________.","a":"have visited","b":"would visit","c":"was visiting","d":"had ever visited","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense: You can use the Present Perfect to describe your experience","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Do you know what ___ from six to eight this morning?","a":"Wilson was doing","b":"Wilson does","c":"Wilson had done","d":"Wilson has done","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple present tense: Speakers occasionally use Simple Present to talk about scheduled events in the near future.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"While Nilson ___ the bulletin, a door somewhere behind him opened.","a":"would stare at","b":"is staring at","c":"was staring at","d":"was stared at","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Past continuous tense: Use the Past Continuous to indicate that a longer action in the past was interrupted. The interruption is usually a shorter action in the Simple Past ( a door....opened).","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"By the time the police arrived, the robbers _________, leaving two guns on the ground outside the store.","a":"fled","b":"have fled","c":"were fleeing","d":"had fled","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: The Past Perfect expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past (the police arrived)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Francis was caught in a traffic jam and by the time she arrived at the airport her teacher's plane ___.","a":"had already taken off","b":"took off","c":"had already been taken off","d":"was taken off","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: The Past Perfect expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past (by the time she arrived) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"The train _________ at the high speed until it reaches the port at about 5:00 p.m.","a":"went","b":"would go","c":"goes","d":"will be going","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Future continuous tense: Use the Future Continuous to indicate that a longer action in the future will be interrupted by a shorter action in the future (until it reaches)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"It _________ in the bus station that Watson met an old friend of his.","a":"has been","b":"is","c":"were","d":"was","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Past simple tense with dummy subject \"it\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"It was not until 10 o'clock that my grandparents _________ to sleep.","a":"was going","b":"had gone","c":"would go","d":"went","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Past simple tense: Use the Simple Past to express the idea that an action started and finished at a specific time in the past","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"He _________ to meet us in front of the McDonald, but he didn't see us.","a":"did went","b":"did go","c":"has gone","d":"didn't go","answer":"2","explain":"Very good! Correct \n- Past simple tense: Use the Simple Past to express the idea that an action started and finished at a specific time in the past: did go =went","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Johnny _________ he could pass the examination but he failed.","a":"thinks","b":"had thought","c":"does think","d":"did think","answer":"2","explain":"\n-Past perfect tense:The Past Perfect expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past (passed- failed)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"}]}